This program will install Bitvise SSH Server 7.15
on the machine it is being run on.

Bitvise SSH Server is an SSH2 server for Windows XP or newer, including
the latest Windows 10 and 2012 R2. Please see www.bitvise.com/ssh-server
for more information.

This program must be run by a user with administrator privileges. If run
without command line options, installation will be performed in interactive
mode. If run with command line options without the '-interactive' option,
installation will be performed in unattended mode.

Usage:
 BvSshServer-Inst -installDir=directory OR -defaultInstance OR -instance=name
                  [-force OR -abortOnWarning[=warning-list-or-mask]
                  [-acceptEULA] [-interactive] [-noRollback]
                  [-renameExistingDir=existingDir]
                  [-activationCode=activation-code-hex]
                  [-keypairs=keypairs-file]
                  [-settings=settings-file]
                  [-instanceTypeSettings=fileName]
                  [-startService]
                  [-startBssCtrl]

 -instance=name: Arbitrary name describing installation instance (without a 
  prefix). The prefix "Bitvise SSH Server - " will be prepended automatically.
 -abortOnWarning[=warning-list-or-mask]: The list or mask of warnings that
  will abort the installation. For example, to abort on warnings 4 and 16
  either use -abortOnWarning=4,16 or -abortOnWarning=20. If neither list
  nor mask is specified, all warnings will be assumed.

To learn more about return codes, execute:
 BvSshServer-Inst -help-codes

IMPORTANT: Applications like the Windows Event Viewer can lock Bitvise SSH
Server files that need to be replaced during an upgrade. If the installer
cannot replace files because they are locked, it will return with exit code
300. This exit code indicates that the installer must be run again using the
same parameters after the computer has been restarted, or after ALL programs
that had locked Bitvise SSH Server files, in any logon session, have been
closed.

